(this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]=this["webpackJsonphacktj-2021"]||[]).push([[10],{161:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),o=a(5),r=(a(61),function(e){var t=e.question,a=e.answer,r=e.small,s=void 0!==r&&r,l=n.useState(!1),i=Object(o.a)(l,2),c=i[0],u=i[1];return n.createElement("li",{className:"question-group ".concat(c?"is-open":"")},n.createElement("h3",{className:"question ".concat(s?"small":""),onClick:function(){return u(!c)}},t,n.createElement("div",{className:"icon icon-plus"}),n.createElement("div",{className:"icon icon-close"})),n.createElement("div",{className:"answer",style:{maxHeight:c?"700px":0}},n.createElement("p",null,a)))});r.defaultProps={small:!1};var s=n.memo(r);a(62),t.default=function(){return n.createElement(n.Fragment,null,n.createElement("a",{className:"anchor",id:"faq",href:"#faq"},"FAQ"),n.createElement("section",{className:"green faq"},n.createElement("div",{className:"container"},n.createElement("h1",{className:"section-title"},"FAQ"),n.createElement("ul",{className:"faq-container"},n.createElement("div",{className:"row"},n.createElement(s,{question:"What is HackTJ?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is a student-run hackathon where you will have 24 hours to learn how to code and/or work with your friends to make your idea come to life.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"When is HackTJ?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ will start on Saturday, November 21 and run until Sunday, November 22.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"Who can attend?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ is open to any and all current high school students. If you're not a high school student but would like to attend, consider coming as a judge, mentor, or volunteer.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"Is there any cost?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"Nope! Thanks to our sponsors, HackTJ is completely free!")})),n.createElement("div",{className:"row"},n.createElement(s,{question:"Is there a deadline?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"Registration for participants, judges, mentors, and volunteers opens on September 25 at 8 p.m. Registration for participants closes on October 16\u2014this is a hard deadline; we do not accept submissions after 8 p.m. Judges, mentors, and volunteers will be able to register until the start of the event.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"Do you have a code of conduct?",small:!0,answer:n.createElement("span",null,"Yes, good question! We have adopted the"," ",n.createElement("a",{href:"".concat("","/conduct.pdf"),target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"MLH code of conduct"),", which all attendees will be required to adhere to.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"Isn't hacking illegal?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,'In the context of a hackathon, "hacking" is to build a real application over the length of the event. It\'s important to not confuse this with illegal hacking, which is gaining unauthorized access to a computer.')}),n.createElement(s,{question:"Do I need a team?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"If you already have a team of 2-4 people you want to work with, that's awesome! If not don't worry because we'll have an opportunity for people to join a team if they need one.")})),n.createElement("div",{className:"row"},n.createElement(s,{question:"What if I don't know how to code?",small:!0,answer:n.createElement("span",null,"Come to HackTJ! Coding is fun, creative, and an important skill, and HackTJ is the perfect way to learn. We'll have workshops and mentors to help guide you.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"What prizes can I win?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,"HackTJ hosts prizes for the best projects in the following categories: Overall Hack, Web App, Mobile App,Design, Social Impact Hack, and Beginner Hack (first-year coder teams). Major League Hacking and some of our partners also host their own Sponsored Prizes, which you can explore when the 7.5 Devpost goes live.")}),n.createElement(s,{question:"How do I register?",answer:n.createElement("span",null,'At 8 p.m. on September 25, a button will appear at the top of the site. Click this, and then you will be redirected to a page where you can click the appropriate form. If you\'re interested in participating as a hacker in HackTJ, click the first button, that says "Participants". Fill out the questions. Near the end, there will be a few questions where you can upload your forms. In order to speed up the registration process, print out these forms, fill them out, and scan them beforehand.')}),n.createElement(s,{question:"How are tickets decisions made?",small:!0,answer:n.createElement("span",null,"Tickets decisisons are made based on a variety of factors, including the registration time. Sign up quickly to increase the chance that you are given a HackTJ 7.5 ticket!")}))),n.createElement("div",null),n.createElement("p",{className:"large bottom-question"},"If your question is not answered here, just ask us:"," ",n.createElement("a",{href:"mailto:hello@hacktj.org",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"hello@hacktj.org"),"."))))}},61:function(e,t,a){},62:function(e,t,a){}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=10.7c117952.chunk.js.map